imyfone.com 2017-05-31

# iMyFone Privacy Policy

iMyFone is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We may share your information only with partners who adhere to iMyFone's commitment to protecting your privacy. iMyFone will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever.

###### Information Collection

When place an order on our website, you may be requested to provide us with certain personally identifiable information includes full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date. The personal information you voluntarily provided will be used to fulfill your request, such as completing transaction, helping us provide better support and services to you.

All purchasers will automatically subscribe to iMyFone Newsletters, and you shall cancel it at any time as you wish.

###### Cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our website and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.

###### Security

We protect the personal information you share with us. For example, if you make an online purchase with RegNow network, they encrypt your credit card number. Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job.

Authorized third parties may need access to some of your personal information. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. We limit such third parties in their access and use of your personal information.

We do not otherwise share your personal information with third parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so.
